<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Buy Bitcoin &#8211; Elite Crypto Consulting</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/category/buy-bitcoin/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com</link>
	<description>Advancing Cryptocurrency Knowledge</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 14:15:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/08/cropped-Logo-final-Colors-03-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Buy Bitcoin &#8211; Elite Crypto Consulting</title>
	<link>https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The value of portfolio management</title>
		<link>https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/the-value-of-portfolio-management/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=the-value-of-portfolio-management</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Elite Crypto Consulting]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 06:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Buy Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/?p=5908</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Elite Crypto Consulting offers personal coaching to help you navigate the complex world of cryptocurrency investing. On Friday, February 8, Bitcoin gained 7.8 percent, signaling another breakout for this famous cryptocurrency. There is significant evidence that other cryptos are set up nicely for a possible run up as well. How does an investor remain objective &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/the-value-of-portfolio-management/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">The value of portfolio management</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/the-value-of-portfolio-management/">The value of portfolio management</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com">Elite Crypto Consulting</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Elite Crypto Consulting offers personal coaching to help you navigate the complex world of cryptocurrency investing.<br />
On Friday, February 8, Bitcoin gained 7.8 percent, signaling another breakout for this famous cryptocurrency. There is significant evidence that other cryptos are set up nicely for a possible run up as well. How does an investor remain objective about balancing his or her investment portfolio? Elite Crypto Consulting discusses the value of portfolio management.</p>
<p><strong>What is portfolio management?</strong></p>
<p>Portfolio management is the operation of making decisions about investment strategy. It takes into account weighing potential investment growth against potential risks. Portfolio management is both an art and a science. It is all about matching investments to objectives and balancing performance against risk.</p>
<p><strong>The key elements of portfolio management are asset allocation and diversification.</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><b>Asset allocation</b>: Combining a variety of assets, such as stocks, bonds, and cash is said to reduce risk in the long term. As some investments outperform others, the different categories of assets provides a greater potential for returns.</li>
<li><b>Diversification</b>: Since it is impossible to consistently predict which investments will gain and which will lose, the best approach is to diversify. Mixing a wide variety of investments is thought to pose a lesser risk and in turn yield higher returns.</li>
</ul>
<p>At Elite Crypto Consulting we will teach you the right way to trade while managing risk. We recognize the value of portfolio management and want to help you learn how to create a balanced portfolio. To help you navigate the world of cryptocurrencies, call the experts at Elite Crypto Consulting today at 1(800) 385-0131.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/the-value-of-portfolio-management/">The value of portfolio management</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com">Elite Crypto Consulting</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>First steps for investing in cryptocurrencies</title>
		<link>https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/first-steps-for-investing-in-cryptocurrencies/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=first-steps-for-investing-in-cryptocurrencies</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Elite Crypto Consulting]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 06:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Buy Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/?p=5906</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Elite Crypto Consulting can help you get started in cryptocurrency with the exchange, wallet, and cryptocurrencies that are right for you. So, you’ve done some research on investing in cryptocurrency, your interest is piqued, and you’re now wondering how to get started. Elite Crypto Consulting outlines the first steps for investing in cryptocurrencies. You&#8217;ll need &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/first-steps-for-investing-in-cryptocurrencies/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">First steps for investing in cryptocurrencies</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/first-steps-for-investing-in-cryptocurrencies/">First steps for investing in cryptocurrencies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com">Elite Crypto Consulting</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Elite Crypto Consulting can help you get started in cryptocurrency with the exchange, wallet, and cryptocurrencies that are right for you.<br />
So, you’ve done some research on investing in cryptocurrency, your interest is piqued, and you’re now wondering how to get started. Elite Crypto Consulting outlines the first steps for <a href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/why-investors-should-consider-cryptocurrencies/">investing in cryptocurrencies</a>.</p>
<p>You&#8217;ll need two things to start investing in cryptocurrency:</p>
<p><strong>1) An exchange</strong><br />
An exchange is where you convert your national currency, like the US dollar, into cryptocurrency. Think of it like the stock exchange. At the New York Stock Exchange, cash is converted into stocks (shares of ownership in various publicly-owned corporations).</p>
<p><strong>2) A wallet</strong><br />
A wallet is where you store the cryptocurrency you’ve purchased with your national currency.</p>
<p><strong>Hardware wallets</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>A hardware wallet is a physical storage device created for holding crypto for the long term. Think of it as a vault. While a hardware wallet is highly secure, it is not the best solution for people who are active traders, because it can take hours or even days to retrieve crypto from them.</li>
</ul>
<p>While these are just the very basic first steps, Elite Crypto Consulting is here to help you get started in cryptocurrency with the exchange, wallet, and cryptocurrencies that are right for you. Let us show you how to trade while managing risk. We offer personal coaching and portfolio management. To help you navigate the world of cryptocurrencies, call the experts at Elite Crypto Consulting today at 1(800) 385-0131.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/first-steps-for-investing-in-cryptocurrencies/">First steps for investing in cryptocurrencies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com">Elite Crypto Consulting</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why hire a professional to help you learn about cryptocurrencies</title>
		<link>https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/why-hire-a-professional-to-help-you-learn-about-cryptocurrencies/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=why-hire-a-professional-to-help-you-learn-about-cryptocurrencies</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Elite Crypto Consulting]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 06:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Buy Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/?p=5904</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Elite Crypto Consulting is your source for cryptocurrency information and portfolio management. An internet search produced this definition of cryptocurrency: “a digital currency in which encryption techniques are used to regulate the generation of units of currency and verify the transfer of funds, operating independently of a central bank.” That definition alone probably best explains &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/why-hire-a-professional-to-help-you-learn-about-cryptocurrencies/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Why hire a professional to help you learn about cryptocurrencies</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/why-hire-a-professional-to-help-you-learn-about-cryptocurrencies/">Why hire a professional to help you learn about cryptocurrencies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com">Elite Crypto Consulting</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Elite Crypto Consulting is your source for cryptocurrency information and portfolio management.<br />
An internet search produced this definition of <a href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/why-investors-should-consider-cryptocurrencies/">cryptocurrency</a>: “a digital currency in which encryption techniques are used to regulate the generation of units of currency and verify the transfer of funds, operating independently of a central bank.” That definition alone probably best explains why you should hire the professionals at Elite Crypto Consulting to introduce you to this complex form of currency.</p>
<p>While most Americans are not intimately familiar with cryptocurrencies, Bitcoin has managed to make a substantial name for itself following its dynamic performance history, making it the most popular among the various currencies. And for all the buzz in the financial world, there is a very small percentage of investors who have actually purchased cryptocurrencies.</p>
<p>A recent survey attempted to discover the primary reasons American investors were not purchasing more Bitcoin and its crypto cousins, Bitcoin cash, Ethereum, Stellar Lumens, Ripple and Cardano. The three most common explanations for not investing in crypto were given as: no interest or need, too risky of an investment, and too complicated.</p>
<p>Of those who have purchased cryptocurrency, the majority did so after having done their own research rather than rely on each currency&#8217;s social media influence. Among those professing to own cryptocurrencies, millennials are at the top, followed by Gen Xers and last, but not least, baby boomers. Of those who plan to purchase crypto in the future, the rankings remain the same.</p>
<p>While many are talking about crypto, many are still very unfamiliar with it. If you&#8217;re intrigued and want to maximize your knowledge about the world of cryptocurrencies, call the experts at Elite Crypto Consulting today at 1(800) 385-0131. Let us show you the right way to trade while managing risk, how to properly store your crypto, and how to manage your portfolio.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/why-hire-a-professional-to-help-you-learn-about-cryptocurrencies/">Why hire a professional to help you learn about cryptocurrencies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com">Elite Crypto Consulting</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Benefits of joining our Elite membership</title>
		<link>https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/benefits-of-joining-our-elite-membership/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=benefits-of-joining-our-elite-membership</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Elite Crypto Consulting]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 15:57:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Buy Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/?p=5850</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Elite Crypto Consulting can help you expand your investment portfolio with cryptocurrency trading. As traders have recently seen, there have been many signals that show an increasing upward momentum in the value of cryptocurrency. Elite Crypto Consulting shares the benefits of joining our Elite membership. We started trading and investing in cryptocurrencies in 2013 after &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/benefits-of-joining-our-elite-membership/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Benefits of joining our Elite membership</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/benefits-of-joining-our-elite-membership/">Benefits of joining our Elite membership</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com">Elite Crypto Consulting</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Elite Crypto Consulting can help you expand your investment portfolio with cryptocurrency trading.<br> As traders have recently seen, there have been many signals that show an increasing upward momentum in the value of <a href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/why-hire-a-professional-to-help-you-learn-about-cryptocurrencies/">cryptocurrency</a>. Elite Crypto Consulting shares the benefits of joining our Elite membership.</p>



<p>We started trading and investing in cryptocurrencies in 2013 after we realized the amazing opportunities they offered. We have enjoyed the yield of our investments and have become experts in the market of cryptocurrency. Our true passion is in trading, which is what inspired us to start Elite Crypto Consulting. At Elite Crypto Consulting, some of the skills we will be happy to share with you include:</p>



<ul><li>The right way to trade while managing risk</li><li>How to properly store your crypto</li><li>How to manage your portfolio</li><li>The different cryptocurrencies and their uses</li><li>Expert knowledge on great investment opportunities</li></ul>



<p>Elite Crypto Consulting offers two membership plans from which you can choose to suit your needs.</p>



<p>Our Premium Membership includes:</p>



<ul><li>Elite Knowledge and Training</li><li>
30-Day Free Trial Period</li><li>
Trade Alerts from the Experts</li><li>
Access to the Elite Trading Room</li><li>
Access to the Elite Mastermind Facebook Group</li><li>
Live Crypto Market Updates</li><li>
Access to the Exclusive Watchlist</li></ul>


<p>Additionally, with our Personalized Coaching, you can:</p>
<ul>
<li>Learn directly from the experts</li>
<li>
Maximize your knowledge</li>
<li>
Receive personal insight from professionals</li>
<li>
Personalize your portfolio</li>
</ul>
<p>Elite Crypto Consulting wants to make you aware of the many benefits our membership provides. If you have been considering including cryptocurrencies as a part of your investment portfolio, our team looks forward to hearing from you. Discover what we can do to help you profit from the new cryptocurrency economy! Call us at 1(800) 385-0131.</p><p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/benefits-of-joining-our-elite-membership/">Benefits of joining our Elite membership</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com">Elite Crypto Consulting</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why investors should consider cryptocurrencies</title>
		<link>https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/why-investors-should-consider-cryptocurrencies/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=why-investors-should-consider-cryptocurrencies</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Elite Crypto Consulting]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 15:52:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Buy Bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/?p=5846</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Elite Crypto Consulting can help you profit from the new cryptocurrency economy. If you follow financial news, you are already aware that cryptocurrency investments have been growing at an exponential rate, proving to be important for diversification in investment portfolios. Elite Crypto Consulting shares why investors should consider cryptocurrencies. Here are a few reasons you &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/why-investors-should-consider-cryptocurrencies/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Why investors should consider cryptocurrencies</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/why-investors-should-consider-cryptocurrencies/">Why investors should consider cryptocurrencies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com">Elite Crypto Consulting</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Elite Crypto Consulting can help you profit from the new cryptocurrency economy.<br> If you follow financial news, you are already aware that <a href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/why-hire-a-professional-to-help-you-learn-about-cryptocurrencies/">cryptocurrency investments</a> have been growing at an exponential rate, proving to be important for diversification in investment portfolios. Elite Crypto Consulting shares why investors should consider cryptocurrencies.</p>



<p>Here are a few reasons you may want to consider investing in cryptocurrencies:</p>



<ul><li><strong> Returns you never could have imagined.</strong> If you had purchased one bitcoin in September 2015 for $231, even after its drop from its December 2017 high, today your investment would be worth more than $3,000. That’s an increase of more than 1198% in a little more than three years! Compare that with the major stock indexes and you’ll be astounded.</li><li><strong>Cryptocurrencies aren’t just Bitcoin</strong>. Bitcoin and Ethereum may be the biggest coins now, but there are hundreds of coins which can bring a gain of similar or even better rates of return. Each coin has a particular purpose or solves a specific problem.</li><li><strong>Huge growth potential</strong>. Gain an advantage over those investors who are reluctant to jump into cryptocurrencies due to their complex nature. When crypto becomes more mainstream, you will realize the benefit of having the experience and knowledge of being an early investor.</li><li> <strong>There is a best time to invest in anything</strong>. Diversification and timing are important in cryptocurrency investing, and that’s where the personalized coaching of Elite Crypto Consulting will be a huge plus for your investment planning. We can help with your timing strategy to achieve the most growth for your investment.</li></ul>



<p>At Elite Crypto Consulting we offer a wide range of services to help introduce you to the fast growing and innovative world of cryptocurrencies, coupled with teaching you how to become an elite trader! We started trading and investing in cryptocurrencies in 2013 after we realized the amazing opportunities they offered. </p>



<p>We are experts on all things crypto and our true passion is in trading, which is what inspired us to start Elite Crypto Consulting. If you have been considering including cryptocurrencies as a part of your investment portfolio, our team looks forward to hearing from you. Discover what we can do to help you profit from the new cryptocurrency economy! Call us at 1-800-385-0131.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com/why-investors-should-consider-cryptocurrencies/">Why investors should consider cryptocurrencies</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.elitecryptoconsulting.com">Elite Crypto Consulting</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
